Eugene Opie Papers ca.1919-1971 Mss.B.Op3
American Philosophical Society
- Correspondence
  - O'Conner, Thomas C. (Box 31)
  - Office of Scientific Research and Development. (Box 31)
  - O'Hearn, Alice (Box 31)
  - Okamoto, Kozo (Box 31)
  - Olch, I Y (Box 31)
  - Olch, Peter D (Box 31)
  - Olcott, Charles T (Box 31)
  - Olinescu, Radu (Box 31)
  - Olitsky, Peter (Box 31)
  - Oliver, Jean (Box 31)
  - Oliver, Wade (Box 31)
  - Opie, Daisy (Box 31)
  - Opie, E.L. (Box 31)
    - Opie, E.L. Charles Russell Bardeen (Box 31)
    - Class sections, 1920-1921 (Box 31)
    - Clippings (Box 31)
    - Control of Tuberculosis in school children (Box 31)
    - D. F. Hochdoerfer, M.D. (Box 31)
    - Exogenous tuberculosis infection of adults (Box 31)
    - Exogenous tuberculosis infection of adults: marital tuberculosis (Box 31)
    - Experimental study of the leucemias and lymphomata (notes) (Box 31)
    - Experiments at Camp Pike (Box 31)
    - Fate of persons in contact with tuberculosis (Box 31)
    - First laboratory of the Rockefeller Institute (Box 31)
    - Influence of tuberculosis in nutrition of children (Box 31)
    - Inter-office correspondence (Box 31)
    - Investigation (Box 31)
    - Investigation of pneumonia and its relation to measles (Box 31)
    - Jamaica autopsies (Box 31)
    - Lectures at Dept. of Pathology (Box 31)
    - Lectures to nurses (Box 31)
    - Letter of resignation from ABMAC (Box 31)
    - Literature of pathology (Box 31)
    - Memorandum, Museum (Box 31)
    - Memorandum on visit to clinic of Dr. Royster (Box 31)
    - Miscellaneous notes (Box 31)
    - Notes (Box 31)
    - Notes on Chinese doctors with respect to ABMAC (Box 31)
    - Notes (White House Conference) (Box 31)
    - Operation of New York Hospital tuberculosis clinic for district (Box 31)
    - Osler as a pathologist (Box 31)
    - Preliminary report of pneumonia.. to surgeon general (Box 31)
    - Prepration of tuberculin solution (Box 31)
    - Recognition and control of tuberculosis of childhood (Box 31)
    - Report of visit to Jamaica. (Box 31)
    - Report on study of protective innoculation against TB in Jamaica (Box 31)
    - Report to Surgeon General on pneumonia (Box 31)
    - Study of TB under auspices of I.H.D. (Box 31)
    - Topics in pathology (Box 31)
    - Transmission of tuberculosis (Box 31)
    - Transportation reimbursements (Box 31)
    - Tuberculosis in Jamaica (Box 31)
    - Tuberculosis of childhood (Box 31)
    - Tuberculosis study in the Bergenland of Austria (Box 31)
  - Opie, Gertrude Simpson (Box 31)
  - Opie, Hierome L. (Box 31)
  - Opie, M J (Box 31)
  - Opie, Margaret (Box 31)
  - Opie, Reginald S (Box 31)
  - Opie, Thomas (Box 31)
  - Opie, Thomas. Medical schools of Baltimore (Box 31)
  - Oppel, Theodore W (Box 31)
  - Oppenheimer, B S (Box 31)
  - Orbison, J Lowell (Box 31)
  - Ordway, William H (Box 31)
  - Osler, Sir William (Box 31)
  - Osler, Sir William, as a pathologist (Box 31)
  - Osterhout, Marian Irwin (Box 31)
  - Oswald, Neville (Box 31)
  - Oswald, Neville. Written work. (Box 31)
  - Ott, Florence C (Box 31)
  - Our Nurses (Box 31)
  - Pagant, Matthew (Box 32)
  - Palade (Box 32)
  - Palmer, Walter W (Box 32)
  - Pancoast, Henry K (Box 32)
  - Pancreas - Duct ligation (Box 32)
  - Pan-European conference (Box 32)
  - Pappenheimer, Alwin M (Box 32)
  - Papworth: Annual report, 1936 (Box 32)
  - Parfitt, C D (Box 32)
  - Paris Chamber of Commerce, "Facts about the war." (Box 32)
  - Park, Edwards A (Box 32)
  - Park, Marion Edwards (Box 32)
  - Park, William H (See also: T.B. Public Health Committee (Box 32)
  - Parker, Bessie A R (Box 32)
  - Parsons, Harriet H (Box 32)
  - Parsons, Robert Jerome (Box 32)
  - Passano Award (Box 32)
  - Pastor, J Rodriguez (Box 32)
  - Pastor, J.R. Tuberculosis in Puerto Rico (Box 32)
  - Pathogenesis inflammation (Box 32)
    - Infestation with entozoa - filterable virus - Fever (Box 32)
    - Inflammation and sclerosis tuberculosis (Box 32)
  - Pathological Society of Philadelphia (Box 33)
  - Pathology (Box 33)
  - Pathology course, second year, roster of (Box 33)
  - Pathology Museum. Classification of diseases affecting organs (Box 33)
  - Pathology Museum. Topographical Schema of classification (Box 33)
  - Pathology - References for a course in (Box 33)
  - Patterson, Winifred (Box 33)
  - Patti, Joseph (Box 33)
  - Paul, John Rodman (Box 33)
  - Payne, John (Box 33)
  - Pearce, N. O. (Box 33)
  - Pearce, Richard Mills (Box 33)
  - Pearl, Raymond (Box 33)
  - Pease, Marshall C (Box 33)
  - Pediconi, Gastone (Box 33)
  - Peffer, Nathaniel. Our distorted view of China (Box 33)
  - Peking Union Medical College (Box 33)
  - Pender, Harold (Box 33)
  - Pendergrass, Eugene P (Box 33)
  - Penn Mutual Life Insurance Company (Box 33)
  - Penniman, Josiah L (Box 33)
  - Pennsylvania Gazette (Box 33)
  - Pennsylvania Company (Box 33)
  - Pennsylvania Conference on tuberculosis (Box 33)
  - Pennsylvania. Department of Public Health, Division of tuberculosis (Box 33)
  - Pennsylvania Society for the Protection of Scientific Research (Box 33)
  - Pennsylvania Tuberculosis Society (Box 33)
  - Pepper, Oliver Hazard Perry (Box 33)
  - Pepper, William (Box 33)
  - Pepper, W. Report of committee on bacteriology appointed. (Box 33)
  - Peretz, Walter (Box 33)
  - Perla, David (Box 33)
  - Perry, Winifred A (Box 33)
  - Perspectives in Biology and Medicine (Box 33)
  - Pettitt, Roswell T (Box 33)
  - Phi Beta Pi Medical Fraternity (Box 33)
  - Philadelphia Bureau of Municipal Research (Box 33)
  - Philadelphia County Medical Society (Box 33)
  - Philadelphia Forte (Box 33)
  - Philadelphia Health Council and Tuberculosis Committee (Box 33)
  - Philadelphia Hospital and Health Survey (Box 33)
  - Philip Morris & Company (Box 34)
  - Phillips, Robert Allan (Box 34)
  - A Philosophical letter to Dr. Opie, from "Susie." (Box 34)
  - Phipps, Henry, Institute (Box 34)
    See also: Henry Phipps Institute, and University of Pennsylvania
  - Phipps Institute Dispensary (Box 34)
    - Dispensary manual (unrevised) (Box 34)
    - District (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 34)
    - Nurses (Box 34)
    - Staff meetings (Box 34)
    - Tuberculosis classification (Box 34)
    - Tuberculosis dispensary, Dr. Putnam (Box 34)
    - Tuberculosis manual (Box 34)
  - Physicians News Service (Box 34)
  - Physiology (Box 34)
  - Pirquet, Clemens V (Box 34)
  - Pithotomy Club (Box 34)
  - Plan of Attack [Jamaica] (Box 34)
  - Plant, J (Box 34)
  - Plotz, Ella Sachs. Foundation for the Advancement of Scientific Investigation (Box 34)
  - Plummer, Susan M (Box 34)
  - Plunkett, Robert E (Box 34)
  - Ueber Diphtherieprophylaxe durch aktive Immunisierung, Pöch, Georg (Box 34)
  - Pope, Alton S. (Box 34)
  - Potter, Truman Squire
  - Pratt, Henry N. (Box 35)
  - Pratt, Joseph A. (Box 35)
  - Presbyterian Hospital, New York (Box 35)
  - Present status of Lee County [Alabama] tuberculosis project (Box 35)
  - Press clippings (Box 35)
  - Preventoria (Box 35)
  - Price, Harry B (Box 35)
  - Program for research on aging (Box 35)
  - Program of Jamaica visit with Dr. Russell (Box 35)
  - Programme of staff conference, Myrtle Bank Hotel, Jamaica (Box 35)
  - Projected investigation...of tuberculosis in the Negro race (Box 35)
  - Protective inoculations - Summaries (Box 35)
  - Proteolytic digestion of the red and white blood corpuscles in the spleen (Box 35)
  - Psychiatry (Box 35)
  - Public Health Nurse (Box 35)
  - Public Health Research Institute for NYC (Box 35)
  - Public Health Research Institute for NYC: Annual reports (Box 35)
  - Public Health...Review of scientific work in progress or planned. (Box 35)
  - Public Health...Meeting of the Research Council Agenda (Box 35)
  - Public Health Research Inst.for NYC. Research Council. (Box 35)
  - Public Relations (Box 36)
  - Public Works Administration (Box 36)
  - Puffer, Ruth Rice (Box 36)
  - Pulmonary Service Manual (Box 36)
  - Putnam, Persis (Box 36)
  - Putnam, Persis (Box 37)
    - An Analysis of the results of tuberculin tests (Box 37)
    - Cottage isolation in Lee County, Alabama (Box 37)
    - Final analysts of data from the Tuberculosis survey in Lee County, Alabama (Box 37)
    - Further aspects of the epidemiology of tuberculosis in Lee County. (Box 37)
    - Memoranda for Dr. Opie (Box 37)
    - Methods employed in sampling clinic records for purposes of study. (Box 37)
    - Report on a study of tuberculosis clinic records in Williamson County, Tenn., and Lee County (Box 37)
    - Spread of tuberculosis in Negro families of Jamaica (Box 37)
    - Statistical analysis of data from the Kingston tuberculosis dispensary (Box 37)
    - Status of tuberculosis studies (Box 37)
  - Rabbit diets (Box 37)
  - Rabinowitsch, Lydia (Box 37)
  - Racquet Club, St. Louis (Box 37)
  - Rappleye, Willard (Box 37)
  - Rathbun, Walter L (Box 37)
  - Ratner, Bret (Box 37)
  - Rawls, P S (Box 37)
  - Recordak Corporation (Box 37)
  - Reed, Lowell J (Box 37)
  - Reed, Ruth V (Box 37)
  - Reif, Arnold E (Box 37)
  - Reis (Box 37)
  - Relation of inflammation to the molecular structure of carbon compounds soluble in the fluids of the body - correspondence (Box 37)
  - Remington-Putnam Book Company (Box 37)
  - Report of co-operative public health work in Jamaica (Box 37)
  - Report of tuberculosis survey in Kingston (Box 37)
  - Report of tuberculosis X-ray laboratory (Box 37)
  - Report of twenty-eighth annual meeting of the Swiss Assoc. for prevention of TB (Box 37)
  - Reprints - E.L. Opie (Box 37)
  - Research Council of the Department of Hospitals, N.Y.C. (Box 37)
  - Research Council of the Department of Hospitals, NYC. Minutes of (Box 37)
  - Research Council of Dept. of Hospitals, NYC, Minutes of annual meeting (Box 37)
  - Research Council of Dept.of Hospitals, NYC, Minutes of executive committee (Box 37)
  - Research Council of Dept. of Hospitals, NYC, Minutes of scientific committee (Box 37)
  - Reynolds Gratz School, tuberculosis in (Box 37)
  - Rheumatic fever (Box 37)
  - Rhoads, C P (Box 37)
  - Rich, Arnold R (Box 37)
  - Richards, Alfred N (Box 37)
  - Richards, E. T. F. (Box 38)
  - Richardson, Russell (Box 38)
  - Richter, Maurice N (Box 38)
  - Richter, Maurice N. Reprints of (Box 38)
  - Riedinger, A Louise (Box 38)
  - Riesman, David (Box 38)
  - Ritter, Verus T (Box 38)
  - Rivas, Damaso de (Box 38)
  - Rivers, Thomas M (Box 38)
  - Roberts, L Gaetan (Box 38)
  - Robertson, H E (Box 38)
  - Robinson, G Canby (Box 38)
  - Robinson, Leland Rex (Box 38)
  - Robinson, William Duffield (Box 38)
  - Rocha Lima, H da (Box 38)
  - Rochester Academy of Medicine (Box 38)
  - Rockefeller, John D (Box 38)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 38)
    - Directory of Officers (Box 38)
    - International Health division (Box 38)
    - Inter. Health Div. Agenda (Box 39)
    - Inter. Health Div. Budget (Box 39)
    - Plan for group insurance, individual (Box 39)
    - Tuberculosis (Box 39)
    - Tuberculosis clinic in Jamaica (Box 39)
  - Rockefeller Institute (also, University) (Box 39)
  - Rockefeller University (Box 39)
    - Correspondence (Box 39)
    - Founding of (Box 40)
    - Hospital - 20th anniversary (Box 40)
    - International Health Division (Box 40)
    - Notes from the Minutes (Box 41)
    - Reports (Box 41)
  - Rogers, Blair O (Box 41)
  - Rogers, Gertrude (Box 41)
  - Rogers, L B (Box 41)
  - Rogers, Stanfield (Box 41)
  - Rolleston, H. D. (Box 41)
  - Rose, Saul B. (Box 42)
  - Roseman, M. J. (Box 42)
  - Rosenow, Edward C (Box 42)
  - Rosenwald, Julius, Fund. Tuberculosis study in Harlem (Box 42)
  - Rothbard, Mary Boon (Box 42)
  - Rothbard, Sidney (Box 42)
  - Rouen Post No. 242 (Box 42)
  - Roulston, Robert B (Box 42)
  - Rous, Peyton (Box 42)
  - Rowe, Allan W (Box 42)
  - Rowe, Julia (Box 42)
  - Rowe, Stuart N (Box 42)
  - Rowell, George C (Box 42)
  - Rowntree, L G (Box 42)
  - Rubin (Box 42)
  - Rudzinska (Box 42)
  - Ruhräh, John (Box 42)
  - Rusch, Harold P (Box 42)
  - The Rush Society (Box 42)
  - Russell, Frederick F (Box 42)
  - Russell, F.F.Projects now under way in Andalusia, Alabama (Box 42)
  - Russell, William L (Box 42)
  - Russell Sage Institute (Box 42)
  - Sabin, Florence Rena (Box 43)
  - Sailer, Joseph (Box 43)
  - St. James Tuberculosis Clinic (Box 43)
  - Saint Louis (Box 43)
  - St. Louis Children's Hospital (Box 43)
  - St. Louis City Hospital (Box 43)
  - St. Louis Medical Society (Box 43)
  - St. Louis Society for the Relief and Prevention of Tuberculosis (Box 43)
  - St. Louis, Missouri. Collector of Revenue (Box 43)
  - Saladé, Robert F (Box 43)
  - Samuels, Bernard (Box 43)
  - Sandoz Pharmaceuticals (Box 43)
  - Sanger, Homer F (Box 43)
  - Sanger, Margaret (Box 43)
  - Satterthwaite, Thomas E (Box 43)
  - Saunders, W. B., Company (Box 43)
  - Saunders, W.B., Co. A Textbook of Pathology by Robert Moore. (Box 43)
  - Sawyer, Wilbur A (Box 44)
  - Sawyer, W.A. Diary notes (Box 44)
  - Saxton, John A, Jr. (Box 44)
  - Scanlon, Daniel R (Box 44)
  - Schneider, Rose Grundfest (Box 44)
  - Schoental, Regina (Box 44)
  - Schooling to 1890 (Box 44)
  - Schooling, Johns Hopkins Univ., 1890-1893 (Box 44)
  - Schooling, College of Physicians and Surgeons of Baltimore, 1893-1894 (Box 44)
  - Schumacher, George A (Box 44)
  - Schwab, Sidney I (Box 44)
  - Schwarz, Henry (Box 44)
  - Schwartz, Irving L (Box 44)
  - Schwarz, Otto (Box 44)
  - Science (Magazine) (Box 44)
  - Science Press Printing Co. (Box 44)
  - Scientific base of the program and the accomplishments of the NTA (Box 44)
  - Scientific Monthly (Box 44)
  - Scope: The Gold Headed Cane. (Box 44)
  - Scott, H William, Jr. (Box 44)
  - Scott, Julian (Box 44)
  - Scrapbook - World War I (Box 44)
  - Scudder, Charles L (Box 44)
  - Seegal, David (Box 45)
  - Seidell, Atherton (Box 45)
  - Seitz, Frederick (Box 45)
  - Selye, Hans (Box 45)
  - Senility - Macy Fund (Box 45)
  - Sferrazza, Josephine (Box 45)
  - Shaffer, Philip A (Box 45)
  - Shannon, James (Box 45)
  - Shapley, Harlow (Box 45)
  - Shaublin, H (Box 45)
  - Shedlowsky, Theo (Box 45)
  - Sheldon, Carol M (Box 45)
  - Sheldon, Paul (Box 45)
  - Shen, S C (Box 45)
  - Sherwood, Mary (Box 45)
  - Sherwood, Noble P (Box 45)
  - Shillingworth, W (Box 45)
  - Shope, Richard E (Box 45)
  - Shope, Mrs. Richard E. (Box 45)
  - Shriver, Alfred Jenkins. Johns Hopkins University murals. (Box 45)
  - Shull, George H (Box 45)
  - Shwartzman, Gregory (Box 45)
  - Sibatani, Atuhiro (Box 45)
  - Siebold, H R (Box 45)
  - Sigma Xi (Box 45)
  - Siler, J F (Box 45)
  - Simmons, A Harvey (Box 45)
  - Simon, Frederick C (Box 45)
  - Simonds, J P (Box 45)
  - Simple tests by which to distinguist gum mixtures from food emulsions (Box 45)
  - Sliva, William (Box 45)
  - Small, James Craig (Box 45)
  - Smillie, Wilson G (Box 45)
  - Smith, Allen J (Box 45)
  - Smith, Charles Hendee (Box 45)
  - Smith, David T (Box 45)
  - Smith, Dorothea E (Box 45)
  - Smith, Edward B (Box 45)
  - Smith, Ellsworth (Box 45)
  - Smith, Francis (Box 45)
  - Smith, Geikie M. (Box 45)
  - Smith, George M. (Box 45)
  - Smith, Hugh H. (Box 45)
  - Protective inoculation for tuberculosis in Jamaica, Smith, Hugh H. (Box 45)
  - Smith, H. P. (Box 45)
  - Smith, Lawrence W (Box 45)
  - A New Textbook of Pathology (Essentials of Pathology), Smith, L.W. (Box 45)
  - Smith, Morgan (Box 45)
  - Smith, O. Norris (Box 45)
  - Smith, Ronald E (Box 45)
  - Smith, Theobald (Box 45)
  - Smith, William Atmar (Box 45)
  - Smoke Prevention Association (Box 45)
  - Smithies, Frank (Box 45)
  - Soberano, Ribas (Box 45)
  - Soby, A M (Box 45)
  - Society for Experimental Biology and Medicine (Box 45)
  - Society of the Arts and Sciences, New York (Box 45)
  - Society of the New York Hospital (Box 45)
  - Soler, Esther C (Box 45)
  - Solis Cohen, Solomon (Box 45)
  - Sommers, Sheldon C (Box 45)
  - Soper, Willard B (Box 45)
  - Special Survey Fund (Box 45)
  - Spencer Lens Company (Box 45)
  - Spotts, S D (Box 45)
  - Squibb, E. R., & Sons (Box 45)
  - Squibb Institute for Medical Research (Box 45)
  - Squier, Gen. (Box 45)
  - Stafford, Frank B (Box 45)
  - Stains (Box 45)
  - Stainsby, W J (Box 45)
  - Stander, H J (Box 45)
  - Starr Centre Association (Box 45)
  - Stebbins, Ernest L (Box 45)
  - Steele, Albert E (Box 45)
  - Steele, Murray (Box 45)
  - Steffen, Gustav (Box 45)
  - Steiner, Walter R (Box 45)
  - Stengel, Alfred (Box 45)
  - Stereofluoroscope (Box 46)
  - Stereofluoroscope Circuit (blue print) (Box 46)
  - Sterling, Julian A (Box 46)
  - Sterling-Winthrop Research Institute (Box 46)
  - Stevens, Helen K (Box 46)
  - Stevenson, Lewis D (Box 46)
  - Stevenson, Virginia E (Box 46)
  - Stewart, David A (Box 46)
  - Stewart, H C (Box 46)
  - Stewart, Harold L (Box 46)
  - Stewart, Irvin (Box 46)
  - Stewart, James J (Box 46)
  - Stewart, Mary C (Box 46)
  - Stewart, Matthew J (Box 46)
  - Stilwell, John (Box 46)
  - Stimson, A M (Box 46)
  - Stimson, Julia C (Box 46)
  - Stivers, Elizabeth S (Box 46)
  - Stockard, Charles B (Box 46)
  - Stoddard, Leland D (Box 46)
  - Stoesser, A V (Box 46)
  - Stokes, John H (Box 46)
  - Stokes, William Royal (Box 46)
  - Stoll, Norman R (Box 46)
  - Stragnell, George (Box 46)
  - Strathairn, G C (Box 46)
  - Straus, Dudley (Box 46)
  - Striker, Cecil (Box 46)
  - Strickler, Albert (Box 46)
  - Strode, George K (Box 46)
  - Strong, Lionell (Box 46)
  - Strong, Richard P (Box 46)
  - Strong, R.P. Investigations upon flagellate infections. (Box 46)
  - Stroud, W D (Box 46)
  - Strumia, Max M (Box 46)
  - Stubbs, Lady (Box 46)
  - Stubbs, E L (Box 46)
  - Student experiment: the biological reactions induced by the administration of the phosphate and wax of the tubercule bacillus (Box 46)
  - Studies of the epidemiology and clinical course of tuberculosis (Box 46)
  - Steubner, Roland W (Box 46)
  - Sturges, Frederick (Box 46)
  - Suggestions as to the application of recently acquired knowledge concerning childhood tuberculosis (Box 46)
  - Sun, Yun Chan (Box 46)
  - Swaab, S M (Box 46)
  - Sweany, H C (Box 46)
  - Sweet, Joshua (Box 46)
  - Sweeting, W E (Box 46)
  - Swift, Homer F (Box 46)
  - Sydenstricker, Edgar (Box 46)
  - Syphilis (Box 46)
  - Syphilis reprints (Box 46)
  - Syphilis study - proposed (Box 46)
  - Syracuse Chamber of Commerce (Box 46)
  - Syracuse Department of Health (Box 46)
  - Sze, Szeming (Box 46)
  - Tanaka, Asazo (Box 46)
  - Tata, Lady, Memorial Trust (Box 46)
  - Tatum (Box 46)
  - Taylor, Howard C (Box 46)
  - Taylor, R M (Box 46)
  - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association (Box 46)
  - [TIAA]: Annual report (Box 46)
  - Technicon Instruments Corporation (Box 46)
  - Templeton, Cora M (Box 46)
  - Ten Broeck, Carl (Box 46)
  - Terry, R J (Box 46)
  - Tershakovec, Maria A (Box 46)
  - Thaysen, Jørn Hess (Box 47)
  - Theory of Retrojection of bile into the pancreas (Box 47)
  - Theory of retrojection of bile into the pancreas. Final. (Box 47)
  - Thomas, Charles C (Box 47)
  - Thomas, Walter S (Box 47)
  - Thompson, Edythe Tate (Box 47)
  - Thompson, Lloyd (Box 47)
  - Thompson, Norma S (Box 47)
  - Tiedemann, E F (Box 47)
  - Tillett, William S (Box 47)
  - Todd, Thomas W (Box 47)
  - Todd, T.W. The color top method... (Box 47)
  - Tolstoi, Edward (Box 47)
  - Torula Infection, by Leo J. Wade (Box 47)
  - Tracy, Martha (Box 47)
  - Traeger, Jules (Box 47)
  - Trotter, Mildred (Box 47)
  - Trout, Hugh H (Box 47)
  - Trudeau, E L (Box 47)
  - Trudeau Medal Committee (Box 47)
  - Trueheart, Elizabeth (Box 47)
  - Tuberculin reaction (Box 47)
  - Tuberculin tests at dispensary (Box 47)
  - Tuberculosis (Box 47)
    - Alabama (See also: T.B. Study in Lee County, AL) (Box 47)
    - Among School Children - advisory committee (Box 47)
    - Catechism (Box 47)
    - Chemotherapy of (Box 47)
    - Clinic, Kingston, Jamaica. Annual report (Box 47)
    - Clinic. Lee County, Alabama (Box 47)
    - Clinic report, New York (Box 47)
    - Complement fixation (Box 47)
    - Conferences (Box 47)
      - Amsterdam
      - Oslo (Box 47)
      - Rome (Box 47)
      - Warsaw (Box 48)
    - Desensitization (Box 48)
    - Development of pulmonary TB in children (Box 48)
    - Discovery and control of (Box 48)
    - Dispensary, Jamaica (Box 48)
    - Dispensary reports (Box 48)
    - dispensary visiting nurses reports (Box 48)
    - District, New York (Box 48)
    - Family graphs and notes on, Jamaica (Box 48)
    - Gooch, Margery (Box 48)
    - Howard, H H (Box 48)
    - Human vaccination (Box 48)
    - In India (Box 48)
    - In Jamaica (Box 48)
    - In Jamaica - physicians reports (Box 48)
    - In Medical Students (Box 48)
    - In Pregnancy (Box 48)
    - Isaacs, E Joyce (Box 48)
  - (Box 49)
    - Jamaica (Box 49)
    - League (Box 49)
    - Lee County, Alabama (Box 49)
    - Lesions (Box 49)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 49)
    - Miscellaneous comparative statistics (Box 49)
    - New York Cattaraugus County. (Box 49)
    - Of school children (Box 50)
    - Patients at Falmouth Poor House (Box 50)
    - Patients at Kingston and St. Andrew poor house (Box 50)
    - Patients at Lucea poor house (Box 50)
    - Patients suffering from, at May Pen poor house (Box 50)
    - Patients at Montego Bay poor house (Box 50)
    - Patients at Portland poor house (Box 50)
    - Patients at St. Ann's Bay poor house (Box 50)
    - Patients at St. Catherine's poor house (Box 50)
    - Patients at St. Mary's poor house (Box 50)
    - Patients at Santa-Cruz poor house (Box 50)
    - Patients at Savanna-la-mar poor house (Box 50)
    - Peiping University Medical College (Box 50)
    - Phipps Institute (Box 50)
    - Preventive (Box 50)
    - Preventive inoculation (Box 50)
    - Preventive inoculation - Resistance - notes (Box 50)
    - Public Health Committee (Box 50)
    - Rats - (Dr. Oswald) (Box 51)
    - Registration and mortality among Manhattan health areas (Box 51)
    - Report of mobile unit (Box 51)
    - Report of X-Ray laboratory (Box 51)
    - Sensitivity (Box 51)
    - Sensitivity and immunity (Box 51)
    - Statistical analysis of Phipps Dispensary examinations - Dr.Putnam (Box 51)
    - Studies fund (Box 51)
  - Tuberculosis study in Lee County, Alabama (Box 51)
    (See also: Tuberculosis. Alabama)
    - Suggestions concerning investigation of, in district around New York Hospital (Box 51)
    - Survey in the West Indies (Box 51)
    - Tennessee (Box 51)
      See also: Tuberculosis. Williamson County, Tenn. This folder contains also material on Jamaica
    - Tests at mental hospital (Box 51)
    - Tests at the dispensary (Box 51)
    - Williamson County, Tennessee (Box 51)
      See also: Tuberculosis. Tennessee
    - Work in Jamaica (Box 51)
  - Tubercumet (Box 51)
  - Tuckes, Augusta. (Box 51)
  - Tucker, Katherine (Box 51)
  - Tuechter, J. L. (Box 51)
  - Tully, Leo P., Jr. (Box 51)
  - Turner, Charles R. (Box 51)
  - Turner, James R (Box 51)
  - Turner, Roy H (Box 51)
  - Typhoid fever (Box 51)
  - Typhoid fever without intestinal lesions (Box 51)
  - United China Institute in America (Box 51)
  - United China Relief (Box 51)
    See also: A.B.M.A.C.: American Bureau for Medical Aid to China
    - Folders 10-43 (Box 52)
    - Folders 44-75 (Box 53)
    - Folders 76-109 (Box 54)
    - Folders 110-142 (Box 55)
  - United China Relief
    - Books and Journals (Box 56)
    - Disbursements committee (Box 56)
    - Medical Supplies for China (Box 56)
    - News (Box 56)
    - Program minutes (Box 56)
    - Report of committee on microfilms (Box 56)
    - supplement (Box 56)
  - United Nations - Tuberculosis (Box 56)
  - United States Army - Autopsies (Box 56)
  - United States Army - Correspondence (Box 57)
  - U.S. Army - List of base hospital laboratory equipment (Box 57)
  - Medical (Box 57)
  - U.S. Daily, supplement: official proceedings of White House Conference (Box 57)
  - U.S. Dept. of Agriculture (Box 57)
  - U.S. Dept. of Health, Education and Welfare (Box 57)
  - U.S. Dept. of State (Box 57)